gurumasterclass.com 2015-08-19

# Privacy | Guru Masterclass

## Who do we contact?

GetAltitude, LLC (ALT) only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products.

## What information do we collect?

ALT collects information in two categories:

### 1\. Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

  * name and e-mail address – provided by you for registration to receive our free newsletters.
  * name, postal address, phone and credit card information – provided by you when purchasing our products.
  * demographic information – used to improve our marketing, products and services.

All such information is strictly protected and used only for delivering the content and products the user has signed up for or purchased, or for finding other men and women who may find our information valuable. This information is NEVER used for other purposes and is NEVER shared with 3rd parties for their own use. The only exception to this could occur if you choose to purchase one of our products via a third party link. Some of the third party partners we work with, offer their own bonus packages when you purchase our product through their promotional link. In order to fulfill on the promised bonus package, we provide them with your name and email address.

The sharing of this information is only for the purpose of bonus fulfillment. We will not share PII that is not necessary to fulfill the purchase you made.

**A note about demographic information:** We contract with information providers that help us better understand people visiting our sites and advertise to those who find our content relevant. We may share PII with such companies provided that they have explicit policies to not share our data with any other parties and solely for the purpose of helping us understand our customers better. This technique is also called “database marketing”. It is practiced by virtually every US corporation. Every US consumer can assume that there is a fair amount of available data about them, including personal data such as buying preferences and education level. There is no central “opt out” place that we are aware of. There are efforts underway to reach a standard that would apply automatically based on browser settings. Regardless of the state of privacy as a whole, you can avoid us finding out extra demographic information about you by doing the following:

  1. email us using our [contact page](http://getaltitude.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us")
  2. in the subject line write: “Privacy – opt out of demographic information”
  3. make sure you enter the same email that you provided as customer or subscriber

### 2\. Anonymous Usage History (non PII)

This information is strictly limited to the history of activities that the user engaged in while on our site. it does NOT include any personally identifiable information (PII). For example, the string “sub+customer” in a cookie (see below for what cookies are) might indicate that you are both a subscriber AND a customer. The purpose of this information is to improve your experience. For example, by storing the fact that you are already a subscriber, we do not need to bother you with an irrelevant subscriber box.

Similarly, by noting that you are a customer, we can “bookmark” the last video frames you watched in our member area and remind you of this the next time you visit. There is a small subset of this history that we use with 3rd parties, such as Google, for the purpose of measuring and improving the efficacy of advertising campaigns. Some of these third parties, aggregate such information across many websites. This allows them to identify users who are more likely to be interested in specific offerings like fashion, sports, education and so on. As an Internet user, you may experience the results of such aggregation by noticing how the ads displayed on Yahoo, for example, better match your interests (the optimistic scenario), or at least more closely match a website that you recently visited. Whether you find this annoying and spooky or helpful and relevant, or perhaps both, you are in good company. This area of Internet advertising is new and controversial.

**Please Note…** (a) third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from your website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads, (b) how users can opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting, and (c) where a user can access a mechanism for exercising such choice (e.g., providing a link to www.aboutads.info/choices).

The tradeoff between privacy vs. commercial efficiency has a long history, for example the “Do not call” list. In any event, it is likely that either the government or the industry will adopt some form of “opt out” capability in the future to address these concerns.

**What are cookies/clear GIFs and how do we use them?** Cookies: Like many other commercial sites, our site utilizes standard technologies called “cookies” and clear GIFs to collect information about how our Site is used. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies were designed to help a website recognize a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the Personally Identifiable information.

**Clear GIFs:** At times, we work with third-party service partners that employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit to help us measure advertising effectiveness. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs are not tied to your Personally Identifiable Information and only track the visitor traffic and behavior to and on our Site. Clear GIFs can “work with” existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company’s clear GIF, the website would match the clear GIFs identifier and the advertising company’s cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the advertising company. We do, at times, provide such information to our third-party advertising service partners, but that information never includes personally identifiable information.

**How do we store your email information?** Your email information (email address, first name) is stored at the list server that delivers ALT newsletters. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive ALT’s newsletters. All of the newsletters that are sent to you by ALT include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by [unsubscribing here](http://getaltitude.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us"). If you have purchased any of my programs, you will continue to receive mailings related to your purchase. If you are an affiliate partner, then you will continue to receive mailings related to our affiliate program. If you would like to be removed from any of these mailings, please [contact my support team](http://getaltitude.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") and they can assist you. **Disclaimer** This policy may be changed at any time at ALT’s discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website. This policy was revised September 19, 2011. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please send us your question by [going here](http://getaltitude.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us"). You may also send a letter to: _GetAltitude, LLC_ _3960 Howard Hughes Pkwy._ _5th Floor_ _Las Vegas, NV 89169_
